mediawebconnect.com 2008-01-08

# - 50 Off

## Privacy Policy

We recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers and have established this Privacy Policy as a result. Full details of our Privacy Policy are included here for your reference.

**Use of Information:**  
We use information we collect from you to process your order. We will not sell, trade, or rent this information to third parties. We may use the information to notify you of upcoming or current offers. When you place an order for a gift certificate, we provide the station with only the name, address, and email address of our customer. The station may use this information to notify you of other promotions. Please note that if any government agency legally requests our customer information, we are obligated to release it.

**Personal Data:**  
When you order from our Web site, we collect the following information from the customer: name, billing/shipping address, telephone number, email address, and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer orders. If we are unable to process an order, this information is used to contact the customer.

**Special Note About Children**  
Children are not eligible to use our website and we ask that minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us or use our site. Media WebConnect has no intention of collecting personal information from children and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age 13. Media WebConnect will use reasonable efforts to delete such information from its database. This site complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). 

**Cookies:**  
A “cookie” is a small file stored by your browser on your computer by a web site. We use temporary cookies to follow the online transaction while they are connected to the web site, they are deleted once the customer leaves the web site and completely closes the browser.

**IP Address and Log Files:**  
We use IP addresses to administer the online transaction. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Security:**  
Media WebConnect is committed to protecting your privacy. We take precautions to protect our customers’ information. When customers submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. When our order form asks customers to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) – which is regarded as the best encryption software in the industry. This technology works best when the site is viewed using Microsoft Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, or Netscape Navigator. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Media WebConnect is committed to taking essential steps to ensure the security of your information.

You may contact us with any further questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy.
